export const quizz = {
    totalQuestions: 42,
    questions: [
        {
            id: 1,
            question: 'Who is the mastermind behind react framework?',
            answers: ['(a) Chrome', '(b) Microsoft Edge', '(c) Facebook', '(d) AWS'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) Facebook',
        },

        {
            id: 2,
            question: 'What is the capital of France?',
            answers: ['(a) Detroit', '(b) Hong Kong', '(c) Abuja', '(d) Paris'],
            correctAnswer: '(d) Paris',
        },

        {
            id: 3,
            question: 'Which of the following is correct about features of javaScript?',
            answers: ['(a) JavaScript is complementary to and integrated HTML', '(b) JavaScript is open and cross-platform',
                        '(c) Both of the above', '(d) All of the above'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) Both of the above',
        },

        {
            id: 4,
            question: 'Which built-in method combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?',
            answers: ['(a) append()', '(b) concat()', '(c) attach()', '(d) None of the above'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) concat()',
        },

        {
            id: 5,
            question: 'Which of the string object is used to find match between a regular expression and a string, and replace the matched substring with a new string?',
            answers: ['(a) concat()', '(b) match()', '(c) replace()', '(d) search()'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) replace()',
        },

        {
            id: 6,
            question: 'Which of the following function of array object reverse the order of the elements of an array?',
            answers: ['(a) reverse()', '(b) push()', '(c) reduce()', '(d) reduceRight()'],
            correctAnswer: '(a) reverse()',
        },

        {
            id: 7,
            question: 'SQL is widely popular because it offers users to access data in the relational database management system',
            answers: ['True', 'False'],
            correctAnswer: 'True',
        },

        {
            id: 8,
            question: 'Who is the founder of Microsoft?',
            answers: ['(a) Steve Jobs', '(b) Bill Gates', '(c) Elon Musk', '(d) Mark Zuckerberg'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) Bill Gates',
        },

        {
            id: 9,
            question: 'What is the largest planet in our solar system?',
            answers: ['(a) Jupiter', '(b) Saturn', '(c) Earth', '(d) Mars'],
            correctAnswer: '(a) Jupiter',
        },

        {
            id: 10,
            question: 'The following are JavaScript frameworks except?',
            answers: ['(a) React', '(b) Vue', '(c) Azure', '(d) Preact'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) Azure'
        },

        {
            id: 11,
            question: 'Who developed Python Programming?',
            answers: ['(a) Wick van Rossum', '(b) Rasmus Lerdof', '(c) Guido van Rosum', '(d) Niene Stom'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) Guido van Rosum',
        },

        {
            id: 12,
            question: 'Which type of Programming does Python support?',
            answers: ['(a) object-oriented programming', '(b) structured programming', '(c) functional programming', '(d) all of the mentioned'],
            correctAnswer: '(d) all of the mentioned',
        },

        {
            id: 13,
            question: 'Is python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?',
            answers: ['(a) no', '(b) yes', '(c) machine dependent', '(d) none'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) yes',
        },

        {
            id: 14,
            question: 'Which of the following is the correct extension of the Python file?',
            answers: ['(a) .python', '(b) .pi', '(c) .py', '(d) .p'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) .py',
        },

        {
            id: 15,
            question: 'What will be the value of the following Python expression? 4 + 3 % 5',
            answers: ['(a) 7', '(b) 2', '(c) 4', '(d) 1'],
            correctAnswer: '(a) 7',
        },

        {
            id: 16,
            question: 'Which of the following is used to define a block of code in Python language?',
            answers: ['(a) indentation', '(b) key', '(c) brackets', '(d) all of the above'],
            correctAnswer: '(a) indentation',
        },

        {
            id: 17,
            question: 'Which keyword is used for function in python language?',
            answers: ['(a) function', '(b) def', '(c) fun', '(d) define'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) def',
        },

        {
            id: 18,
            question: 'Which of the following character is used to give single-line comments in python?',
            answers: ['(a) //', '(b) #', '(c) !', '(d) /*'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) #',
        },

        {
            id: 19,
            question: 'What will be the output of the following python code? i = 1 while True: if i%3 == 0: break print(i) i + =1',
            answers: ['(a) 1 2 3', '(b) error', '(c) 1 2', '(d) none'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) error',
        },

        {
            id: 20,
            question: 'Python supports the creation of anonymous functions at run time, using a construct called-------?',
            answers: ['(a) pi', '(b) anonymous', '(c) lambda', '(d) none'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) lambda',
        },

        {
            id: 21,
            question: 'What are SDLC models available?',
            answers: ['(a) waterfall model', '(b) iterative model', '(c) v-model', '(d) all of the above'],
            correctAnswer: '(d) all of the above',
        },

        {
            id: 22,
            question: 'Verification is a term that refers to the set of activities which ensure software implements a specific function',
            answers: ['True', 'False'],
            correctAnswer: 'True',
        },

        {
            id:23,
            question: '------ uses an iterative process that relies on cyclic patterns with a high degree of collaboration?',
            answers: ['(a) functional programming', '(b) agile methodologies', '(c) validation', '(d) none'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) agile methodologies',
        },

        {
            id: 24,
            question: 'Refactoring is the process of taking care of existing code and restructuring it, typically to improve the code through small changes without altering its underlying behavior',
            answers: ['True', 'False'],
            correctAnswer: 'True',
        },

        {
            id: 25,
            question: 'Which of the following statements should be used to obtain a reminder after dividing?',
            answers: ['(a) rem = 3.14 % 2.1', '(b) rem = modf(3.14,2.1)', '(c) rem = fmod(3.14,2.1)', '(d) Reminder cannot be obtain in floating division'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) rem = fmod(3.14,2.1)',
        },

        {
            id: 26,
            question: 'What are types of linkages?',
            answers: ['(a) internal and external', '(b) external,internal,and none', '(c) external and none', '(d) internal'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) external,internal, and none',
        },

        {
            id: 27,
            question: 'Which of the following special symbol allowed in a variable name?',
            answers: ['(a) *(asterisk)', '(b) |(pipeline)', '(c) -(hyphen)', '(d) _(underscore)'],
            correctAnswer: '(d) _(underscore)',
        },

        {
            id: 28,
            question: 'How would you round off a value from 1.66 to 2.0?',
            answers: ['(a) ceil(1.66)', '(b) floor(1.66)', '(c) roundup(1.66)', '(d) roundto(1.66)'],
            correctAnswer: '(a) ceil(1.66)',
        },

        {
            id: 29,
            question: 'Statements: No women teacher can play. Some women teachers are athletes Conclusions: I. male athletes can play II. some athletes can play',
            answers: ['(a) only conclusion I follows', '(b) only conclusion II follows', '(c) either I or II follows', '(d) neither I or II follows'],
            correctAnswer: '(d) neither I or II follows',
        },

        {
            id: 30,
            question: 'Statements: I. All the schools in the area had to be kept closed for most part of the week II. Many parents have withdrawn their children from the local schools',
            answers: ['(a) statement I is the cause and statement II is the effect', '(b) statement II is the cause and statement I is the effect', '(c) both statement I and II are independent causes', '(d) both statement I and II are effects of independent causes'],
            correctAnswer: '(d) both statement I and II are effects of independent causes',
        },

        {
            id: 31,
            question: 'Look at the series what number should come next? 2,1,(1/2),(1/4),......',
            answers: ['(a) (1/3)', '(b) (1/8)', '(2/8)', '(d) (1/16)'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) (1/8)',
        },

        {
            id: 32,
            question: 'SCD, TEF, UGH, ----, WKL',
            answers: ['(a) CMN', '(b) UJI', '(c) VIJ', '(d) IJT'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) VIJ',
        },

        {
            id: 33,
            question: 'Which word does NOT belong with the others',
            answers: ['(a) parsley', '(b) basil', '(c) dill', '(d) mayonnaise'],
            correctAnswer: '(d) mayonnaise',
        },

        {
            id: 34,
            question: 'desert',
            answers: ['(a) cactus', '(b) arid', '(c) oasis', '(d) flat'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) arid',
        },

        {
            id: 35,
            question: 'Two bus tickets from city A to B and three bus tickets from city A to C cost 77USD but three bus tickets from city A to B and two tickets from city A to C cost 73USD. What are the fares for cities B and C from A?',
            answers: ['(a) 4USD,23USD', '(b) 13USD,17USD', '(c) 15USD,14USD', '(d) 17USD,13USD'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) 13USD,17USD',
        },

        {
            id: 36,
            question: 'An institution organized a fete and 1/5 of the girls and 1/8 of the boys participated in the same time. What fraction of the total number of students took part in the fete?',
            answers: ['(a) 2/13', '(b) 13/40', '(c) data inadequate', '(d) none'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) data inadequate',
        },

        {
            id: 37,
            question: 'Which of the following two entities(reading from left to right) can be connected by the dot operator?',
            answers: ['(a) A class member and a class object', '(b) A class object and a class', '(c) A class and a member of that class', '(d) A class object and a member of that class'],
            correctAnswer: '(d) A class object and a member of that class',
        },

        {
            id: 38,
            question: 'Which of the following type of class allows only one object of it to be created?',
            answers: ['(a) virtual class', '(b) abstract class', '(c) singleton class', '(d) friend class'],
            correctAnswer: '(c) singleton class',
        },

        {
            id: 39,
            question: 'Which of the following statement is true about constructors?',
            answers: ['(a) if we provide a non-argument constructor then the compiler still provides a zero-argument constructor', '(b) static constructors can use optional argument ', '(c) overload constructors cannot use optional arguments', '(d) if we do not provide a constructor,then the compiler provides a zero-argument constructor'],
            correctAnswer: '(d) if we do not provide a constructor,then the compiler provides a zero-argument constructor',
        },

        {
            id: 40,
            question: 'Which of the following is NOT an Arithmetic operator in C#.NET?',
            answers: ['(a) **', '(b) +', '(c) /', '(d) %'],
            correctAnswer: '(a) **',
        },

        {
            id: 41,
            question: 'Which four options describe the correct default values of array elements of the types indicated? (1)int->0 (2)string->"null" (3)dog->null (4)char->u0000 (5)float->0.0f (6)boolean->true',
            answers: ['(a) 1,2,3,4', '(b) 1,3,4,5', '(c) 2,4,5,6', '(d) 3,4,5,6'],
            correctAnswer: '(b) 1,3,4,5',
        },

        {
            id: 42,
            question: 'Did you enjoy the Quiz?',
            answers: ['Yes', 'No'],
            correctAnswer: 'Yes',
        },
    ],
};